A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Press Materials FA1322
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Record Group 2, Accession 2018:088, 1953-2002; 2; 32.15 Cubic Feet 34 LTR size, 1 Half-LTR size, 40 LGL size, and 1 Half-LGL size Hollinger boxes
  - Press clippings, 1953-2002; 2; 21.9 Cubic Feet 10 LTR size, 38 LGL size, and 1 Half-LGL size Hollinger boxes
    - Clippings, 2000-2002; 5; 4.35 Cubic Feet About 8.75 LGL size Hollinger boxes and 1 Half-LGL size Hollinger box
      - Luce Media Report and press clippings, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 1514)
      - General press clippings, 2001-2002 (Box 74, Folder 1515-1516)
      - Innovations in American Government Awards Program, 2001 December (Box 74, Folder 1517)
      - Leadership for a Changing World Awards Program (LCW), 2001 (Box 74, Folder 1518)
      - Osama bin Laden, 2001 November 29 (Box 74, Folder 1519)
      - Disaster relief, 2001 December (Box 74, Folder 1520)
      - Fellowships, 2001 December (Box 74, Folder 1521)
      - Education, Media, Arts, and Culture Program (EMAC), Education, Knowledge, and Religion (EKR), 2001 November-December (Box 74, Folder 1522)
      - Education, Media, Arts, and Culture Program (EMAC), Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), 2001 December (Box 74, Folder 1523)
      - Peace and Social Justice Program Program (PSJ), Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), 2001 December (Box 74, Folder 1524)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Community and Resource Development, 2001 December (Box 74, Folder 1525)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Economic Development, 2001 December (Box 74, Folder 1526)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), 2001 November-December (Box 74, Folder 1527)
      - International Fellowships Program (IFP), 2000 (Box 75, Folder 1528-1529)
      - Leadership for a Changing World Awards Program (LCW), 2001 September (Box 75, Folder 1530)
      - Leadership for a Changing World Awards Program (LCW), 2001-2002 (Box 75, Folder 1531-1532)
      - General press clippings, 2001-2002 (Box 75, Folder 1533)
      - Innovations in American Government Awards Program, 2001-2002 (Box 75, Folder 1534)
      - Leadership for a Changing World Awards Program (LCW), 2001 January 28 (Box 75, Folder 1535)
      - Fellowships, 2001 January (Box 75, Folder 1536)
      - Education, Media, Arts, and Culture Program (EMAC), Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), 2001-2002 (Box 75, Folder 1537)
      - Education, Media, Arts, and Culture Program (EMAC), Education, Knowledge, and Religion (EKR), 2001 January (Box 75, Folder 1538)
      - Peace and Social Justice Program Program (PSJ), Governance and Civil Society (GCS), 2001 (Box 75, Folder 1539)
      - Peace and Social Justice Program Program (PSJ), Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), 2001 January 29 (Box 75, Folder 1540)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Community and Resource Development, 2001-2002 (Box 75, Folder 1541)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Economic Development, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 1542)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), 2001 (Box 75, Folder 1543)
      - September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2002 January (Box 75, Folder 1544)
      - General press clippings, 2002 July-August (Box 75, Folder 1545)
      - General press clippings, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 1546)
      - Burrelle's and Luce press clippings and announcements, 2001 May-August (Box 75, Folder 1547)